you have to offer no resistance overcomes the hardest substances that
您不必提供抵抗力即可克服最坚硬的物质
which offers no resistance and enter weather is still space
没有阻力，进入天气还是空间
view in the world can compliment the teaching with adwords or support the
世界各地的视图可以补充adwords的教学内容或支持
value of nam action
南行动的价值
death note proof that i truly and in love what fid the
死亡笔记证明，我真正地和爱上了什么
round off the shirt pyncheon 5 and 6 century bc
对公元前5世纪和公元前6世纪的衬衫pyncheon进行四舍五入
which makes a contemporary of computers nevertheless the charlie's savior
这使得计算机成为了当代，但查理是救世主
sheds red and masterpiece god the old
流下红色和杰作神老
circles de my work or douwes him oh well known concept that enzyme murch van
圈我的工作或杜威他oh众所周知的概念，酶霉菌范
douwes philosophy is how we act as cambuur translator tasman
Douwes哲学是我们作为cambuur翻译tasman的方式
effortless action or the paradox kool action of in an action in a practical
毫不费力的动作或实际动作中的悖论库尔动作
sense we can describe wow s so time or flow or a referred
我们可以用时间或流量来描述哇
to as such a by apple something really liter and son
像这样的苹果真的东西升和儿子
d and gauge in action is also the oldest driving and move to time and space
d和具轨距也是最古老的行驶方式，并向时空移动
almost effortlessly de arno extremes no worries noémie nations
几乎毫不费力地将阿尔诺极端化，没有后顾之忧
everything seems to flow in a natural course as an introduction to the
一切似乎都是顺理成章地作为介绍
beautiful tradition or there is an old like to present you
美好的传统或古老的礼物
the philosophy or flow
哲学或流程
[Music] the dao de jing is my stereo space of
[音乐]倒的景是我的立体声空间
art natto leader snoke consensus from exec
纳豆艺术领袖嘲笑高管的共识
lee it was written what the existence of the software
李这是写什么软件的存在
romanian de spirit nevertheless one thing is certain de
罗马尼亚精神仍然是一件事
profanity of this work has left it smart community to this day
这项工作的亵渎行为使它至今仍是一个聪明的社区
not to mention that the dao de jing is the most translated work in the world
更不用说《道德经》是世界上翻译最多的作品
literature after the bible the essence of our
圣经之后的文学是我们的精髓
philosophy is living in harmony with the language as the w rolls
随着世界的发展，哲学正在与语言和谐相处
so what is the room this question week and rooney and char and the futile to
那么这个问题周的房间是什么，鲁尼和查尔，以及徒劳无益的
try or understanding of the language only go as
尝试或理解该语言只能
far as the limitations of for perception
就感知的局限性而言
the dew becomes who is and it becomes looks feels
露水变成了谁，它变得看起来像
smells of sound like remains and mystery but about the download to speak of is it
听起来像是残留物和神秘的声音，但是关于下载的内容呢？
the real daal account pilots man's famous opening
真正的达尔帐户飞行员的著名开幕
or the dao de jing chose like this de down that can be described
还是道德静选择像这样的唐纳德可以形容
is not the journal daal de take it cammie ghosts is not the journal
不是日记daal de take it cammie ghosts不是日记
take and quote thus knowledge is available about the dew
采取并引用，因此可获得关于露水的知识
well the dew knew philosophers and forsyth about and the overhead and that the throne room
露水很好地了解了哲学家和连贯性以及头顶上的东西，宝座室
is already a campus in force that is beyond of comprehension and cannot be
已经是一个难以理解的校园，无法
perceived by the senses and even though you can never grass
被感官所感知，即使你永远也不会草
the throne room the goal is to live and growing with hats strikingly similar
王座室的目标是生活和戴着相似的帽子一起成长
to the story cup road to nature keeps your life in harmony with the way down
通往故事之路通往大自然的道路使您的生活与下坡路融为一体
with the literature that won its three league practicon
赢得了三届联赛冠军的文学作品
effort to achieve this however you can find many monastery point legislation
努力实现这一目标，但是您可以找到许多修道院要点立法
stillness of mind grabbing the census be in trade and the cessation of striving in
进行人口普查的心态在贸易中和努力进取的停止
order to openers els up to two were kings of the universe this stillness of
为了揭幕战，多达两个是宇宙之王。
a mind thousand necessarily mean that had to sit down somewhere with her
一千个心意一定意味着必须和她一起坐下
eyes closed the dew clears on surf that stillness or
闭上眼睛，露水清除了冲浪的静止感或
mind can be combined with action and if your complete lee in the present moment
头脑可以与行动结合起来，如果你在此时此刻全力以赴
actions will go effortlessly whatever friction and accompanied by eraser
无论摩擦如何，动作都会毫不费力地进行，并伴有橡皮擦
shopfocus so macho it is all I had to be strong at
shopfocus真是男子气概，这是我所必须具备的全部优势
biography retired professional basketball player
传记退休的职业篮球运动员
bill russell right it was almost as if you're playing in slow motion
比尔·罗素（Bill russell）对，几乎就像是在慢动作播放
through a box of pelts keep atomos sense 'explosion fells and were next shot would
通过一盒毛皮保持原子感“爆炸性皮脂”，下一次射击会
be sign and quote the towers become vogue she comes a she story about a crook
签名并引用塔楼成为时尚，她来了一个关于骗子的故事
the team takes how in cupcakes in the work well in a state or flow
团队以状态或流程来了解如何在工作中良好地使用纸杯蛋糕
this crashes the attention of lord and who was the most about how elegantly
这引起了主人的注意，谁是最优雅的人
the biscuit cut-up boxem when commenting two men skills cooking is laid down
放下评论两个男人烹饪技巧时的饼干切割盒
knife and replied care about is the who knows you chose
刀和回答关心的是谁知道你选择了
behance kill when first known god and on action
当第一个认识神并行动时就杀人
all the driver was the action itself after 3 years
所有驾驶员都是3年后的行为本身
arno lommers oliebol rocks and then i'll now go edit by spirit and don't look at
arno lommers oliebol岩石，然后我现在按精神去编辑，不看
my eyes perception and understanding of you coming
我的眼睛对你来的感知
step en spirit had to wear at once a go along with the natural make-up
step en spirit必须与自然妆容同时搭配
strike in de beek hollows garden life molenbeek openings and following links
罢工de beek空心花园生活molenbeek开口和以下链接
sdhc level touch the smallest song my pie and the
sdhc级触摸我的馅饼和
margin lessons to my joint and squad and essential part of the story
我的联队和班级的边际课程，也是故事的重要组成部分
the conditioner is the knife that the cuckoo users those cities the cuckoos
护发素是杜鹃使用者在那些城市杜鹃的刀
change your life's ever you because they caught
改变了你的一生，因为他们被抓住了
and mediocre cooks change the maize and freemont
平庸的厨师改变了玉米和自由山
lucas de heck good thing however was using the same live for my team you
卢卡斯·德·赫克（Lucas de Heck）好事了，但是我为我的团队使用了同一个直播
because i used with skills and salty this story connects to another
因为我习惯于技巧和咸味，所以这个故事与另一个故事有关
essential teaching of douwes and how it is the power of gentleness in forcing and
杜威的基本教义，以及柔和的力量如何迫使和
striving to might get the job done but at the same time you spend much more
努力做到可能会完成工作，但与此同时您要花更多的钱
energy than necessary and possibly software from collateral damage when
多余的能量，可能会在附带损坏时造成软件损坏
other hand someone in estate of flow uprose septas
另一方面，有人在流动中上升了隔垫
kindly elegantly want to act and what not to find a balance between
优雅地想表现自己和什么之间找不到平衡
action and an action is a meter of nature had not too cold is the code pair
动作和动作是自然界的一米，不是太冷就是代码对
between anxiety and board him the idea behind and an action
在焦虑和登上他背后的想法和行动之间
evil arts western ideal of forcing and working harder and harder to get who
西方邪恶艺术逼迫和努力工作的理想
even how your encouraged to be and business to take control and to strive
甚至是您如何受到鼓励，以及企业如何控制和努力
at least many people software of the pression
至少有很多人使用该软件
anxiety disorders and sleep disorders are burning or even out who look down
焦虑症和睡眠障碍正在燃烧甚至看不起的人
on pc and off mistake it read aloud what that soldier front frank's
在电脑上，错误地读出来，大声读了那个士兵前弗兰克的
when look at nature doing nothing mix way more sense third mutants frank
当看大自然无所作为时，第三种突变体更加坦率
we even pretend that i'm joking with the amount of energy
我们甚至假装我是精力充沛的人
results of the consequence of cherrys of actions
一连串的后果的结果
the funny thing about this is that many of the sections came
有趣的是，许多部分
naturally and the teske thousand not millions of intervention then
自然而然地，千千万万而不是几百万的干预
necessary to stay right into the right direction is so that many problems
保持正确方向的必要是很多问题
of them even dew is a commercial life to we river river already has a
他们甚至露水对我们来说都是商业生活，河水河已经有了
course of several courses and jones gryffindor even in that river we can
即使在那条河中，我们也可以通过几个课程和琼斯·格兰芬多的课程
swim most famous current week and hollandtoer branch of week and let go and
游泳最著名的当前周和本周的hollandtoer分支，放手
go along with the stream master of life's how smart i wished cord and who
跟生活的流媒体大师一起，我希望索德有多聪明，以及谁
don't even an realize it or mind believes that it can and should control
甚至没有意识到它或头脑相信它可以并且应该控制
the enforcement in order to survive what you skye and or egocentric I as the
为了使您生存下来，或以我为中心的自我生存
a vast majority of processes within is sometimes even an outsider and also arnold
内在的绝大多数过程有时甚至是局外人，也是阿诺德
control-m in les vzw death control ar bodily processus spot digestion leaf flea
les vzw的Control-m死亡控制身体过程斑点消化叶跳蚤
or the healing of wood wood and control other people
或治愈木柴并控制其他人
i don't control the future we do t control how i fall in love toys and more
我不控制未来，我们不控制我如何爱上玩具等等
people refined attractive everything outsider of faculties just
人们提炼出引人入胜的一切教职员工
in tucson direction chose some times forbes at intelligence met
在图森方向上选择了一些福布斯在情报会议上
mostly in a natural course one who follow along with the current how you
通常是自然路线，跟随当前潮流的人
eyeliner even what is just records' this is the pope or reads resistance and gifts
眼线笔甚至只是记录'这是教皇或阅读抵抗和礼物
no chance to grieve and feel cold as resisting it like that
没有机会因为抗拒而感到悲伤和寒冷
de douwes 2 is rather navigating through the river and dies tryin to control at
de douwes 2相当在河中航行，死于tryin以控制
something that will never work and although respect of travel
永远不会工作的东西，尽管尊重旅行
that correct arises douwes him is the water myself
正确出现杜威他是我自己的水
the characteristics of water ar softness and the unity that basically symbolized
水ar柔软度的特征和基本象征的团结
auris church oh here's a quote from the dead jean
奥里斯教堂，哦，这是死去的牛仔的名言
the supreme god is low mud was benefits already of creation
至高无上的上帝是泥巴已经是创造的好处。
we would be trying to compete we gathers fat eats in a popular places that it
我们将尝试竞争，在一个受欢迎的地方收集脂肪类食物，
is like the language and quote ladder medisoft is it about opportunity
就像语言和报价阶梯medisoft就是机会
harmens which we can see indian ocean of rock and warder not only six faithful
我们可以看到印度洋的岩石和看守的危害，不仅六个忠实的
readers it also has no purpose google nose specifically design or get it
读者也没有目的专门设计或得到它的谷歌鼻子
knows everything that basis is incredible
知道一切基础都是不可思议的
life force at liter of oil a thousand cold work but without any ambition what there is
一千升油的生命力寒冷的工作，但没有雄心壮志
so if test and most uding substance get enough and is better than water for it
因此，如果测试和大多数含糊的物质摄入足够，并且比水还好
overcoming de hart en ridgid de kast nothing can compete we vet en quote
克服挑战，没有竞争可以胜任我们的报价
if you ever experienced estheet of flow nerf long feng with disperse and oil
如果您曾经体验过带有分散剂和油的nerf long feng美容师
comes back be vinkik mind tags back control this
回来是vinkik介意标签回来控制这个
the focus on results is safer than the task at hand
专注于结果比手头的任务更安全
this reminds me of the story concept of amorfati
这让我想起了amorfati的故事概念
wedgwood comments because their graced the outcome whatever it may be and instead
韦奇伍德（Wedgwood）评论，因为无论结果如何，他们都会夸大结果，而不是
of learning about the future focusing on what's in the present no
关于未来的学习专注于现在的情况
matter if you're completely im merced in sports riding a video game for tensing
您是否完全沉迷于骑电玩游戏的运动中
when in the cities or you will flow for category
在城市中的时候，否则您将流向类别
the pressure die anxiety about the future de velinx of the best is just you and de
关于最好的未来发展的压力消磨着你和你
task at hand your complete ie in the present and the
您即将完成的任务，即现在和现在
only way to do this is by letting go let it go
做到这一点的唯一方法是放手
least at swimmin agents current step holding on to some rangers
至少在swimmin代理人当前的步伐保持在一些游骑兵身上
the least letting go of the past letting go of the future
至少放开过去放开未来
focus on this moment entirely and just leave it without hesitation
完全专注于这一刻，毫不犹豫地离开
thank you for watching
谢谢你的收看
[Music]
[音乐]
yes [Music]
是的[音乐]